United States Presidential Railroad Commission documents 5003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States. Presidential Railroad Commission documents
1960-1962.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States. Presidential Railroad Commission.
5003
40.06 cubic feet
15.3 linear ft.
Transcripts, exhibits, and studies.
Consist of the transcript of the hearings, exhibits presented by carriers and unions, and studies prepared by the staff of the Commission.
3109222
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Ann L. Mann
Date completed:
1969
EAD encoding:
Casey S. Westerman, August 15, 2002
Biographical / Historical
The U.S. Presidential Railroad Commission was established by Executive Order No. 10891 of November 1, 1960, to consider a controversy between carriers represented by the Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, the Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, and the Switchmen's Union of North America.
Specifically, the controversy surrounded the assertion by the carriers that firemen were not needed on diesel locomotives and that their positions should be eliminated. The unions, on the other hand, maintained that modern diesel locomotives were much too complex to be operated by one engineer and that firemen were necessary to ensure safety. Seventy-nine witnesses appeared before the Commission and statements were filed on behalf of one hundred and fifty-five additional witnesses.
Scope and Contents
Consist of the transcript of the hearings, exhibits presented by carriers and unions, and studies prepared by the staff of the Commission.
Related Materials
5526. United States. Presidential Railroad Commission. Arbitration Board 282.
Arrangement
I. Proceedings, 1960-1961.
Boxes 1-15
II. Labor union exhibits, 1960-1961.
Boxes 16-25
III. Carrier exhibits, 1960-1961.
Boxes 26-35
IV. Staff documents, 1960-1961.
Boxes 38-41
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Mediation and conciliation, Industrial--United States--Cases.; Unemployment, Technological--United States.; Locomotive engineers.; Locomotive firemen.; Railroad employees.; Memorabilia.; Photographs.; Proceedings.; Color slides.; Transcripts.; United States.; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers.; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen.; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen.; Eastern Carriers' Conference Committee.; Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen.; Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committee.; Switchmen's Union of North America.; Western Carriers' Conference Committee.
3109222
- I. Proceedings, 1960-1961., Consist of the transcript of the hearings, exhibits presented by carriers and unions, and studies prepared by the staff of the Commission.
  - Vol. 1 pp. 1-100 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 1 pp. 101-196 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 2 pp. 197-298 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 2 pp. 299-403 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 3 pp. 404-515 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 3 pp. 516-628 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 4 pp. 629-726 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 4 pp. 727-820 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 5 pp. 821-895 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 5 pp. 896-964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 6 pp. 965-1040 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 6 pp. 1040-1091 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 7 pp. 1092-1164 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 7 pp. 1165-1233 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 8 pp. 1234-1304 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 8 pp. 1305-1377 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 9 pp. 1378-1479 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 10 pp. 1480-1573 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 11 pp. 1574-1648 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 11 pp. 1649-1714 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 12 pp. 1715-1790 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 12 pp. 1791-1862 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 13 pp. 1863-1941 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 13 pp. 1942-2024 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 14 pp. 2025-2101 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 15 pp. 2102-2164 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 15 pp. 2165-2226 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 16 pp. 2227-2348 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 17 pp. 2349-2401 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 17 pp. 2402-2473 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 18 pp. 2474-2575 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 19 pp. 2576-2644 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 19 pp. 2645-2727 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 20 pp. 2728-2800 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 20 pp. 2801-2876 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 21 pp. 2877-2963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 22 pp. 2964-3039 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 22 pp. 3040-3119 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 23 pp. 3120-3199 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 23 pp. 3200-3284 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 24 pp. 3285-3369 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 24 pp. 3370-3474 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 25 pp. 3475-3544 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 25 pp. 3545-3633 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 26 pp. 3634-3716 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 26 pp. 3717-3815 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 27 pp. 3816-3900 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 27 pp. 3901-3987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 28 pp. 3988-4084 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 29 pp. 4085-4150 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 29 pp. 4151-4231 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 30 pp. 4232-4299 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 30 pp. 4300-4385 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 31 pp. 4386-4480 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 32 pp. 4481-4534 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 32 pp. 4535-4615 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 33 pp. 4616-4675 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 33 pp. 4676-4772 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 34 pp. 4773-4859 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 34 pp. 4860-4955 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 35 pp. 4956-5029 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 35 pp. 5030-5113 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 36 pp. 5114-5179 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 36 pp. 5180-5258 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 37 pp. 5259-5329 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 37 pp. 5330-5403 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 38 pp. 5404-5516 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 39 pp. 5517-5579 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 39 pp. 5580-5658 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 40 pp. 5659.5726 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 40 pp. 5727.5807 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 41 pp. 5808-5889 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 41 pp. 5890-5970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 42 pp. 5971-6063 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 42 pp. 6064-6162 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 43 pp. 6163-6252 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 44 pp. 6253-6339 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 44 pp. 6340-6394 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 45 pp. 6395-6469 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 45 pp. 6470-6535 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 46 pp. 6536-6600 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 46 pp. 6601-6695 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 47 pp. 6696-6749 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 47 pp. 6750-6828 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 48 pp. 6829-6880 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 48 pp. 6881-6961 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 49 pp. 6962-7030 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 49 pp. 7031-7116 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 50 pp. 7117-7199 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 50 pp. 7200-7293 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 51 pp. 7294-7379 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 51 pp. 7380-7443 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 52 pp. 7444-7510 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 52 pp. 7511-7585 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 53 pp. 7586-7649 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 53 pp. 7650-7745 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 54 pp. 7746-7829 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 54 pp. 7830-7907 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 55 pp. 7908-7999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 55 pp. 8000-8056 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 56 pp. 8057-8139 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 56 pp. 8140-8206 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 57 pp. 8207-8299 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 57 pp. 8300-8413 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 58 pp. 8414-8499 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 58 pp. 8500-8562 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 59 pp. 8563-8639 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 59 pp. 8640-8742 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 60 pp. 8743-8840 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 60 pp. 8841-8945 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 61 pp. 8946-9069 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 61 pp. 9070-9187 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 62 pp. 9188-9319 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 62 pp. 9320-9445 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 63 pp. 9446-9549 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 63 pp. 9550-9649 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 64 pp. 9650-9719 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 64 pp. 9720-9787 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 65 pp. 9788-9879 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 65 pp. 9830-9974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 66 pp. 9975-10099 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 66 pp. 10100-10201 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 67 pp. 10202-10299 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 67 pp. 10300-10397 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 68 pp. 10398-10505 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 69 pp. 10506-10579 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 69 pp. 10580-10663 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 70 pp. 10664-10769 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 70 pp. 10770-10826 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 71 pp. 10827-10889 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 71 pp. 10890-10958-A (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 72 pp. 10959-11029 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 72 pp. 11030-11103 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 73 pp. 11104-11169 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 73 pp. 11170-11235 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 74 pp. 11236-11299 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 74 pp. 11300-11364 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 75 pp. 11365-11401 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 76 pp. 11402-11479 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 76 pp. 11480-11548 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 77 pp. 11549-11619 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 77 pp. 11620-11702 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 78 pp. 11703-11799 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 78 pp. 11800-11906 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 79 pp. 11907-12000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 80 pp. 12001-12099 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 80 pp. 12100-12159 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 81 pp. 12160-12270 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 81 pp. 12271-12332 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 82 pp. 12383-12449 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 82 pp. 12450-12514 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 83 pp. 12515-12599 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 83 pp. 12600-12666 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 84 pp. 12667-12759 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 84 pp. 12760-12865 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 85 pp. 12866-12999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 85 pp. 13000-13078 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 86 pp. 13079-13199 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 86 pp. 13200-13297 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 87 pp. 13298-13399 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 87 pp. 13400-13524 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 88 pp. 13525-13599 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 88 pp. 13600-13655 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 89 pp. 13656-13749 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 89 pp. 13740-13860 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 90 pp. 13861-13952 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 90 pp. 13953-14052 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 91 pp. 14053-14149 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 91 pp. 14150-14256 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 92 pp. 14257-14339 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 92 pp. 14340-14429 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 92 pp. 14430-14511 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 93 pp. 14512-14599 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 93 pp. 14600-14699 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 93 pp. 14700-14822 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 94 pp. 14823-14939 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 94 pp. 14940-15055 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 95 pp. 15056-15160 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 95 pp. 15161-15260 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 96 pp. 15261-15339 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 96 pp. 15340-15419 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 96 pp. 15420-15503 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 97 pp. 15504-15506 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- II. Labor union exhibits, 1960-1961., Include 121 of the 134 exhibits submitted to the Commission by the unions.
  Scope and Contents
  Included are studies, reports, statistical compilations, arbitration awards, work rules, examinations, agreements, photographs and other documentation bearing on manning issues, wages and fringe benefits, safety, and job security in the railroad industry, and special allowances in the airline industry, as well as comparative data with other forms of transportation. Also rebuttal testimony to carrier exhibits and statements. Substantive documents relate to the New York Central System, the Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad, and the Missouri Pacific Lines, among others.
  - Exhibits 1-2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 3-4 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit 6, Photos H 1-11, Slides H 2-11 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit 7, Photos AA 1-17 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit 9 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit 11 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits 13-18 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Exhibit 19, Photos L 1-31, Slides L 1-32 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Exhibit 20, Photos 1-40, Slides 1-40 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit 21, Photos C 1-18, Slides C 1-18 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit 22, Photos E 1-34, EX 1-12, Slides E 1-34, EX 1-12 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit 23, Photos J 1-54, Slides J 1-54 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit 24, Photos R 1-20, Slides R 1-17 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit 26 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Exhibit 27, Photos IKS 1-6 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Exhibits 28-30 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Exhibit 31, Photos Y 1-23, Slides Y 1-23 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit 32, Photos O 1-33, Slides O 1-31 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit 33, Photos S 1-31, Slides S 1-31 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit 34, Photos Q 1-24, Slides Q 1-24 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit 35, Photos F 1-53, Slides F 1-53 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit 37, Photos CC 1-22 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit 38, Photos A 1-30, Slides A 1-30 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit 39, Photos B 1-29, Slides B 1-29 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit 42, Photos V 1-45, Slides V 1-45 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit 43, Photos P 1-56, Slides P 1-56 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit 44, Photos X 1-16, Slides X 1-16 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Exhibit 52 A (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit 52 B (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit 53 A (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit 53 B (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit 53 C (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit 53 D (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit 53 E (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit 54 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit 55 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 56-59 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 60-61 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 62-64 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit 65 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 66-67 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 68-69 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 70-73 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits 74-77 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Exhibits 78-80 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 81-84 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 85-87 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 88-91 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 92-95 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 96, Photos EE 1-32 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 97-98, Photos DD 1-10 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 99, Photos BB 1-21, Slides 1-21 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 100 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 103-109 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 110-115 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 116-117 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 118-119 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 120-132 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- III. Carrier exhibits, 1960-1961., Consist of 187 carrier exhibits.
  Include studies, awards, statements, statistical data, photographs, and other documentation relating to the firemen manning issue, working conditions on the railroads, accidents, labor costs, the job content of train service employees and engineers, and testimony rebutting union arguments. Substantive documents relate to the New York Central System, the Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, the Louisville and Nashville Railroad, the Netherlands Railways, the Canadian Pacific Railroad, the Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio Railroad, the Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, the Boston and Maine Railroad Company, the Illinois Central Railroad, the Great Northern Railway, and the Pennsylvania Railroad, among others.
  - Exhibits 1-3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 3A (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 3B, 3C, 3D (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit 5 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit 6 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit 7 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit 8 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit 9 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit 10c, 10cx (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit 11,12 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits 13-15 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 16-18 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 19-21 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 22,23 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 24 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 25, 26 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits 27,28 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 29-31 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 32-34 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 35-37 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 38,39 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 40-41 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits 42,43 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 44, 45 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 46, 47 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 49-51 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 52-55 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 56-59 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits 60-62 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 63,64 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 65-67 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 68,69 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 70,71 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 72,73 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits 74-7? (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 78-81 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 82 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 83-86 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 87,88 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 89,90 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits 91,92 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 93, 94 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 95-99 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 100-102 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 103-105 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 106,107 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits 108 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Exhibits 109 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 110 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 111-116 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 117-119 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 120,121 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 122,123 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits 124-126 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Exhibits 127,128 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Exhibits 129 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Exhibits 130,131 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits 134-136 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits 137-139 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits 140-143 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits 144-147 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits 148-151 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- IV. Staff documents, 1960-1961., Consist of documents that were gathered and prepared by the Commission's staff. They include "A Study of the Railroad Industry's Pay Structure," "A Study of Work Rules and Practices," and "A Study of the Impact of Railroad Mergers," among others.
  - Studies Relating to Operating Employees.
    - Pay Structure of Railroad Operating Employees.
      - Volume 1. Louisville and Nashville Railroad (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Volume 2. Louisville and Nashville Railroad (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Volume 1. Chicago, Burlington, Quincy Railroad (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Volume 2. Chicago, Burlington, Quincy Railroad (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Volume 3. Chicago, Burlington, Quincy Railroad (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Volume 1. Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Volume 1. Sample of 31 Glass 1 Railroads (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Volume 2. Sample of 31 Glass 1 Railroads (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Volume 3. Sample of 31 Glass 1 Railroads (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Volume 5. Sample of 31 Glass 1 Railroads (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Volume 6. Sample of 31 Glass 1 Railroads (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Volume 7. Sample of 31 Glass 1 Railroads (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Volume 8. Sample of 31 Glass 1 Railroads (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Volume 9. Sample of 31 Glass 1 Railroads (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - (a) Minutes of Technical and Research Staff Public, Management and Labor: Observation Trips for Public Members on preceding "Sample of 31 Railroads." (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Partial Impact by Cities Railroad Mergers (Box 40A, Folder 1)
  - Press Release, February '23 (Box 40A, Folder 2)
  - Statement by H. E. Wilmarth, Council-5 Railroad (Box 40A, Folder 3)
  - Table Press Release Organizations, Answers to Carriers, Questions re: (Box 40A, Folder 4)
  - Organization, Proposal (Box 40A, Folder 5)
  - P.R.C. Press Release (Box 40A, Folder 6)
  - Rules and Practices Covering, Operating Employees (Box 40A, Folder 7)
  - Material Introduced but not Identified as Exhibits (Box 40A, Folder 8)
  - Report 1962 Exhibit "A" (Box 40A, Folder 9)
  - Penna. Ky. v. Droscoll ET AL. (Box 40A, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Material (Box 40A, Folder 11)
  - Background of Proceeding, Wage and Rule Structure National Railroads (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Appendix Vol. 1 Index-Digest to the record of the commission's hearings (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Appendix Vol. 2 Pay structure, railroad operating employees (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Selected Tables and Comments -- from Pay Structure Study-Appendix 2 An analysis of the undervaluation of basic rates-from Pay Structure Study (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Impact of earnings of railroad operation employees of P.R.C. Pay Structure Recommendations (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Memorandum of meeting of the labor members of the commission on April 17, 1961, with counselors Wilmarth and Henslee (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Appendix Vol. 3 Studies relating to railroad operating employees. No. 2-5. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Appendix Vol. 4 Studies relating to collective bargaining agreements and practices outside railroad industry. No. 6-22. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Report of the Presidential Railroad Commission. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Dissent of Commissioner S.C. Phillips P.R.C. (Box 41, Folder 10)